In this clip not only are we going to add fancy foot work but we're going to show what we do with our hands at the same time.
It requires coordination.
It takes time with African dance.
If you don't get it automatically, that's okay.
It isn't something that just happens over night.
It takes a lot of practice and years of instruction abd just sticking with it.
So, the last clip, two, three, one, two, three.
So we're going to go up.
When we lift on our left foot, one, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three.
One, two, three, lift, one, two, three, lift your hands.
One, two, three, it's a fist.
One, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three.